accessinfohub.com 2013-05-11

# 

If you do not agree to the Terms of Use, discontinue using the site immediately! 

The following terms govern and apply to all the web pages, web sites, domain names, their sub-domains and sub-directories that relate to and constitute the property of **AccessInfoHub.com**. 

By using any of the sites of **AccessInfoHub.com** , you signify your Assent and Agreement to these Terms of Use. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, do not use the sites. 

|  This Privacy Policy Notice governs the use of the web page at and its associated services, web pages, domains and sub-domains, which are **owned and operated by ** ** **AccessInfoHub.com******** ("Owner"). Wherever this Notice refers to "users" it means "you", while "we" or "our" refer to ******AccessInfoHub.com****** and "Web Site" for the web site in which the page belongs. 

At AccessInfoHub.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by AccessInfoHub.com and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, AccessInfoHub.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user?s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
AccessInfoHub.com does not use cookies. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on AccessInfoHub.com. .:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to AccessInfoHub.com and other sites on the Internet. .:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .... Google Adsense  
Commission Junction  
Clickbank  
Chitika  
Amazon 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on AccessInfoHub.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

AccessInfoHub.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. AccessInfoHub.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**Provision about Children**

We do not collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. We encourage parents to go online with their kids. Click [here](http://www.onguardonline.gov/topics/kids-privacy.aspx) to check out the FTC's site for more tips on protecting children's privacy online.
